fabartdiy.com 2016-06-26

# Privacy Policy

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines our privacy policy when you use FabArtDIY.com, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

This privacy policy governs the manner in which FabArtDIY.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from visitors (“Users”) of FabArtDIY.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by FabArtDIY.com.

**Privacy Policy – Personal Information**

FabArtDIY.com collects personally identifiable information from the users to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a _voluntary_ basis may include name, email address, telephone number.

This information is collected if you request information from us, sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.

Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will **not be sold or provided to third parties.**

**Privacy Policy – Use of Cookies and Web Beacons**

We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site’s services, a cookie enables FabArtDIY.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.

FabArtDIY.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Notice Regarding Online Behavioral Advertising**

We allow third party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site.  These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g. click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.  To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice visit the NAI at [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on FabArtDIY.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to FabArtDIY.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Amazon…

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on FabArtDIY.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

FabArtDIY.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. FabArtDIY.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of many websites. The above experiences are common to every website on the internet and not specific to FabArtDIY.com.

**Privacy Policy – Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act**

This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. However, the content of our site is family friendly, ‘G’ Rated. We operate our site in compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

**Privacy Policy – Non-Personal Information**

In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

**Privacy Policy – Release of Information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding Users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Privacy Policy – How You Can Correct or Remove Information**

We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please click on this link and use our Contact Us page.

**Privacy Policy – Updates and Effective Date**

FabArtDIY.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.

**Privacy Policy – Agreeing to Terms**

If you do not agree to FabArtDIY.com Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site. Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.

### DMCA Policy.

Have you been wrongly credited or someone submitted your project/image? We respect  **[DMCA takedowns](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Digital_Millennium_Copyright_Act)** from all publishers/copyright holders, [drop us a message ](http://www.fabartdiy.com/contact-us/)and expect a response and content removal within 24 hours.
